[EN] Na maioria das vezes
[EN] é tipo, eu não sei,
[EN] é como se houvesse uma
[EN] espessa nuvem negra cobrindo tudo.
[EN] Como se víssemos o mundo, mas
[EN] realmente não víssemos o mundo, sabe?
[EN] Estamos todos apenas tropeçando, sem direção,
[EN] sem senso de significado, sem senso de propósito.
[EN] Eu sei que isso pode parecer super deprimente,
[EN] mas honestamente, acho que é uma coisa boa.
[EN] Porque nos faz
[EN] apreciar as outras vezes.
[EN] Aqueles breves, transcendentes
[EN] momentos em que as luzes piscam,
[EN] as partes da nuvem negra, e você
[EN] vê o mundo
[EN] pelo que ele realmente é.
[EN] E de repente há um significado.
[EN] De repente, há um propósito.
[EN] Então, uh, você... oh, merda, merda,
[EN] merda, merda, merda, merda, merda, merda.
[EN] Se tiver sorte, experimentará
[EN] isso uma vez na vida.
[EN] Caramba, isso foi,
[EN] uh, isso foi bom.
[EN] Para mim, tão suave.
[EN] Aconteceu duas vezes.
[EN] A primeira foi no dia
[EN] em que conheci Josh.
[EN] Uh, eu sou o Josh.
[EN] Eu sou Lyra.
[EN] E o segundo,
[EN] no dia em que o matei.
[EN] Iris, acorde.
[EN] Ooh, está um dia lindo
[EN] Ooh, eu nunca
[EN] me senti
[EN] assim antes de sair.
[EN] Ooh.
[EN] Quanto tempo fiquei fora?
[EN] Uh, por um tempo.
[EN] Sim, você foi zonked
[EN] lá fora muito bem.
[EN] Eu estava tendo o
[EN] sonho mais maravilhoso.
[EN] Sim? Sobre mim?
[EN] Isso é muito presunçoso, mas...
[EN] Sim.
[EN] Sim, você sabia.
[EN] Foram tempos sensuais?
[EN] Não. Você é desviante.
[EN] Um pouco de sensualidade?
[EN] Não.
[EN] A minha camisa estava despida?
[EN] Não, eu estava sonhando com
[EN] o dia em que nos conhecemos.
[EN] Também era perfeito.
[EN] Lembra-se de como
[EN] tudo era perfeito?
[EN] Sim, não, não, como
[EN] eu poderia esquecer?
[EN] Supermercado, as laranjas.
[EN] Que estrada é essa?
[EN] Não aparece no GPS.
[EN] Não acho que este
[EN] seja o caminho.
[EN] Acho que esta pode ser
[EN] a entrada da garagem.
[EN] O dia está lindo.
[EN] Ah, eu nunca me
[EN] senti assim antes
[EN] Vou te dar um pouco mais.
[EN] Oh, bem, estou a
[EN] sentir-me tão bem
[EN] Chegou ao seu destino.
[EN] Obrigado, carro do Josh.
[EN] Obrigado, carro.
[EN] Abra o porta-malas.
[EN] Apareça no porta-malas.
[EN] Que merda!
[EN] Cat chamou este lugar de
[EN] pequena cabana
[EN] rústica na floresta.
[EN] Acho que podemos ter diferenças
[EN] opiniões sobre o significado
[EN] da palavra "cabine".
[EN] Também rústico.
[EN] Também pouco.
[EN] O quê?
[EN] Iris, vamos. Você
[EN] sabe que não pode
[EN] minta para mim. Diga-me
[EN] o que há de errado.
[EN] Vou fazer algo estúpido.
[EN] Eu vou dizer algo
[EN] estúpido. Vou envergonhá-lo.
[EN] Eles vão rir de mim.
[EN] Eles vão me odiar.
[EN] Eles já me odeiam.
[EN] Jesus Cristo.
[EN] Planeamos esta viagem há meses,
[EN] e tudo isso acabou
[EN] de sair agora,
[EN] a 6 metros da porra da porta?
[EN] Olha, olha. Ei.
[EN] Meus amigos não te odeiam.
[EN] O gato tem.
[EN] Sim, talvez, mas o
[EN] gato odeia todo mundo.
[EN] Eu só não quero estragar tudo.
[EN] Vamos, Beboop. Você
[EN] não vai estragar tudo.
[EN] "Apenas relaxe.
[EN] Sabe? Não seja todo
[EN] mal-humorado e esquisito.
[EN] Lembre-se...
[EN] lembre-se de
[EN] sorrir e agir feliz.
[EN] Certo?
[EN] Certo.
[EN] Oba! Você fez com
[EN] que fosse engraçado!
[EN] Ok, então quando disse
[EN] "remoto", pensei que
[EN] quisesse dizer, tipo,
[EN] a alguns quilómetros
[EN] da autoestrada.
[EN] Não sabia que queria dizer
[EN] borda da porra da civilização.
[EN] Não seja tão dramático,
[EN] Josh. Não é tão longe.
[EN] Certo. Difícil discordar.
[EN] Olá, Iris.
[EN] Oi, Cat. É tão bom te ver.
[EN] So good.
[EN] Pessoal, olhem
[EN] quem eu encontrei.
[EN] Ei, ei...
[EN] Olha para ti na cozinha, meu.
[EN] Olhe para mim. Bem-vindo.
[EN] Eu te daria um abraço,
[EN] mas tenho mãos de vieira.
[EN] Desculpa. Ok? Bem, eu agradeço.
[EN] Onde está essa Ayþe?
[EN] Ah, aí está ele.
[EN] Joshy boy, Joshy boy
[EN] "Olá, amigo."
[EN] Como é que vocês duas entraram?
[EN] Olá. Olá. Tudo bem?
[EN] Estou bem. Uh,
[EN] estou, hum, bêbado.
[EN] Bom. Isso é bom.
[EN] Ah, e Josh, lembra-se do Sergei?
[EN] Privyat.
[EN] Ei! Sergei, prazer
[EN] em vê-lo novamente.
[EN] Da mesma forma, meu
[EN] amigo. Da mesma forma.
[EN] E esta bela
[EN] criação deve ser Iris.
[EN] Olá.
[EN] Que prazer. Eu ouvi
[EN] muito sobre este.
[EN] Sério? Tudo bem, espero.
[EN] Sua casa no lago, é...
[EN] É realmente... É incrível.
[EN] Sim. Sim. É tão isolado.
[EN] Quero dizer, acho que
[EN] o último lugar em que
[EN] passou foi, tipo,
[EN] dez milhas de volta.
[EN] Dezessete. E eu paguei por isso.
[EN] Mas tenho um lugar que
[EN] não sai barato, meus amigos.
[EN] Nada barato.
[EN] Não me diga que
[EN] está no lago todo.
[EN] Não, não, não. Não seja boba.
[EN] Apenas todo o terreno em torno dele.
[EN] Mas vamos buscar
[EN] uma bebida para vocês.
[EN] O que você gosta?
[EN] Cerveja, coquetel, vinho?
[EN] Estou bem. Mais do que
[EN] tudo, só preciso de um banho.
[EN] Katunak, em que
[EN] quarto eles estão?
[EN] Subindo as escadas, no final
[EN] do corredor. O último à esquerda.
[EN] Vejo você depois.
[EN] Sorria.
[EN] Ficar feliz.
[EN] Ok, continue.
[EN] Continue a história.
[EN] Então, eu estava a usar isto
[EN] traje ridiculamente
[EN] elaborado do Drácula.
[EN] E eu não conhecia uma
[EN] única pessoa, como eu disse.
[EN] Então, estou ao lado do lanche
[EN] mesa, apenas mastigando cenouras
[EN] e algo que parecia homus.
[EN] Não era homus.
[EN] Não era homus, eu não acho.
[EN] Mas sinto um tapinha no ombro.
[EN] E então eu me viro.
[EN] E tem esse verde, inchado
[EN] dinossauro apenas me encarando.
[EN] E dentro da cabeça
[EN] dele, eu ouço isso muito,
[EN] uma voz muito abafada
[EN] e muito irritada diz:
[EN] "Você está na minha cola."
[EN] Então eu me viro, olho
[EN] para baixo, e com certeza,
[EN] Estou de pé na sua
[EN] pequena cauda de dinossauro.
[EN] Então eu saio e peço
[EN] desculpas, e ele arranca a cabeça.
[EN] E eu estou a olhar para o máximo
[EN] homem bonito que
[EN] eu já vi na minha vida.
[EN] Então, você conheceu este belo
[EN] homem depois de conhecer Eli?
[EN] Ok, de jeito
[EN] nenhum. Cale a boca.
[EN] Aquilo era uma vieira?
[EN] Aquilo era uma vieira.
[EN] Isso realmente me atingiu.
[EN] Sim. Eu joguei beisebol.
[EN] — Sim, você disse.
[EN] Quando soube?
[EN] Eu sei o quê.
[EN] Aquele... era ele.
[EN] Não. Bem ali.
[EN] Eu sei que vai soar
[EN] brega, mas no momento...
[EN] No momento em que bloqueamos
[EN] algo dentro de mim, ele só...
[EN] clicado no lugar.
[EN] Não parece nada brega. Entendi.
[EN] É como se houvesse
[EN] um pedaço de você
[EN] que nem sabia que
[EN] estava quebrado,
[EN] E então...
[EN] de repente está...
[EN] está consertado.
[EN] E você está a olhar
[EN] para este estranho,
[EN] essa pessoa que
[EN] nunca conheceu antes,
[EN] Sabes,
[EN] que para o resto da sua
[EN] vida, você vai fazer
[EN] o que for preciso
[EN] para fazer essa pessoa feliz.
[EN] Certo? Sim. Sim.
[EN] Sim, com certeza.
[EN] Patrick, esta comida é
[EN] inacreditável. Obrigado.
[EN] Obrigado, Sergey. Isso é tão
[EN] gentil da sua parte. Fico
[EN] feliz que tenha gostado.
[EN] Ele me estraga. Juro que ganhei
[EN] uns 5 quilos desde que
[EN] começamos a namorar.
[EN] Apenas 10%!
[EN] Cala a boca.
[EN] Então, Sergey, que
[EN] tipo de trabalho você faz?
[EN] Ah, você sabe, eu tenho
[EN] dedos em muitos potes.
[EN] Minhas mãos não
[EN] estão limpas, meu amigo.
[EN] É um... um negócio muito sujo.
[EN] Sergey parece...
[EN] ele parece legal.
[EN] Ah, sim. Ele tem tudo o
[EN] que você quer num homem.
[EN] Ele é rico, inteligente.
[EN] Ele tem uma linda esposa.
[EN] Esposa? Ele... Sergey é casado?
[EN] -
[EN] Mas vocês se amam...
[EN] vocês se amam.
[EN] Com amor? Não. Não,
[EN] não, não, não, não.
[EN] Teria que pensar em mim
[EN] como um ser humano primeiro.
[EN] "Não estou entendendo."
[EN] Eu sou um cúmplice.
[EN] Como a merda do carro dele.
[EN] Eu visto o que ele
[EN] quer, como o que
[EN] ele quer, foda-se
[EN] quando ele quiser.
[EN] Mas...
[EN] Olha com quem estou falando.
[EN] Não gosta de mim, Kat?
[EN] Sabe, não é que eu
[EN] não goste de você, Iris.
[EN] É a sua ideia.
[EN] Fez-me sentir tão...
[EN] substituível.
[EN] Substituível?
[EN] Ninguém poderia
[EN] substituí-la, Kat.
[EN] Quero dizer, tu és a Kat.
[EN] O senhor é tão
[EN] destemido. É inspirador.
[EN] Quem me dera poder
[EN] ser mais como tu, mas...
[EN] Sabe, eu não fui
[EN] construído assim.
[EN] Eu só...
[EN] Eu sinto que há sempre
[EN] algo dentro de mim me segurando.
[EN] Não, não, não.
[EN] Aham.
[EN]  Vamos lá.
[EN] Okay, get out
[EN] of the pitch. Saia.
[EN] Oh, God.
[EN]  Vamos lá.
[EN] You two, put that phone
[EN] away. Guarde -o e levante -se.
[EN] Get your asses up. Vamos.
[EN] Come on.
[EN]  Ei, querida.
[EN] I'm so glad we did this.
[EN] Estar aqui com você é
[EN] simplesmente perfeito.
[EN] I don't know.
[EN] Sinto muito se estava sendo
[EN] estranho ou mopey mais cedo.
[EN] I just want you
[EN] to be happy, Josh.
[EN]  isso é tudo.
[EN] All right. Vá dormir.
[EN] It's such a gorgeous day out.
[EN]  Onde está o tempo?
[EN] It's currently 72 graus, mas o
[EN] 93% de chance de chuva à noite.
[EN] It never gets old.
[EN]  você quase pronto?
[EN] I'm sorry, babe. Eu penso Eu preciso de algum
[EN] tempo para tomar banho e   bate alguns galões de café.
[EN] Why don't you head
[EN] down there by yourself?
[EN]  foi a sua ideia.
[EN] You said you wanted a nice,
[EN] relaxing morning by the lake.
[EN] eu sei, mas isso é antes
[EN] a ressaca me alcançou.
[EN] Last night was a lot.
[EN]  você encontraria isso certo?
[EN] Of course I did, Bebo.
[EN]  ontem à noite foi incrível.
[EN] You want me to wait?
[EN] Podemos fazer o
[EN] chuveiro para dois.
[EN] No, no, no. Tudo bem.
[EN] You go on ahead.
[EN] Aproveite o máximo
[EN] deste lindo dia possível.
[EN] Okay.
[EN]  Dobre utre.
[EN] Sorry?
[EN]  isso significa bom dia.
[EN] Oh, yes.
[EN]  Dobre utre para você também.
[EN] Hey, your Russian is not bad.
[EN]  não é bom.
[EN] But also it is not bad.
[EN]  Vista agradável.
[EN] Lovely boy to love.
[EN]  hmm. You like?
[EN] Eu realmente vou
[EN] voltar para dentro.
[EN] So soon?
[EN]  sim.
[EN] Josh wasn't feeling
[EN] great this morning,
[EN] so I think I should
[EN] check in on him.
[EN] O garoto grande de Josh
[EN] pode cuidar de si mesmo.
[EN] Thay keeps her company.
[EN] Eu realmente acho
[EN] que deveria vê -lo.
[EN] You like Lake House, yes?
[EN]  sim.
[EN] You enjoy your time here?
[EN]  mm-hmm. Yeah, very much.
[EN] então como convidado,
[EN] por favor fique.
[EN] Keep the soul of
[EN] Russian men company.
[EN]  ok.
[EN] Wonderful.
[EN]  oh.
[EN] You mind?
[EN] Acabei de voltar e
[EN] ombros é difícil de alcançar.
[EN] Don't want to get too tan.
[EN]  ok.
[EN] Hmm.
[EN]  e ombros, por favor.
[EN] Okay.
[EN]  O que você está fazendo?
[EN] It's no problem.
[EN]  A ideia deste gato.
[EN] She tells Sergey você
[EN] está aqui embaixo.
[EN] Give Sergey permission.
[EN]  Vou com minha mão, por favor.
[EN] This is what you do,
[EN] É para isso que você é.
[EN] Please, please stop.
[EN]  Eu estava bêbado.
[EN] I mean, last night.
[EN] sim, sim, você estava
[EN] extremamente bêbado.
[EN] It was crazy. Você
[EN] também estava bêbado.
[EN] Like more drunk than I am.
[EN]  eu estava mais bêbado.
[EN] I was more hydrated.
[EN]  como se fosse este presente.
[EN] Like people get bloated
[EN] and stuff and not me.
[EN]  Como nunca acontece.
[EN] Never gets loaded.
[EN]  nunca. Like I just like I get
[EN] uma bebida e faça
[EN] o que eu quiser.
[EN] Like I'm looking at dehydrated.
[EN]  Sim, é como, que porra?
[EN] Oh shit.
[EN]  Iris?
[EN] What the fuck?
[EN]  eu não queria.
[EN] He forced himself on me.
[EN]  Quem fez?
[EN] Sergey?
[EN]  por favor.
[EN] Sergey just want a little taste.
[EN]  Eu só queria que ele parasse.
[EN] Oh God, Sergey.
[EN]  Iris, Iris, olhe para mim.
[EN] Look at me.
[EN]  Fale -me através disso.
[EN] What happened?
[EN]  Eu disse, pare!
[EN] I didn't have a choice.
[EN]  Sergey.
[EN] Bats!
[EN]  falador.
[EN] He wouldn't let go.
[EN]  ele estava me sufocando, Josh.
[EN] And then I...
[EN]  e então você o quê, íris?
[EN] Then you what?
[EN]  ele estava tentando me matar.
[EN] And the only thing I could
[EN] think about was that if he
[EN] me matou, eu
[EN] nunca mais te veria.
[EN] And I heard so much more
[EN] than the pain of being choked.
[EN] eu não deixaria
[EN] isso acontecer.
[EN] I couldn't let him take
[EN] me away from you.
[EN]  eu te amo muito.
[EN] Let's go to sleep.
[EN] tem certeza que
[EN] isso vai segurar?
[EN] Yeah.
[EN]  Não, tudo bem.
[EN] She's not superhuman
[EN] or anything.
[EN] ela é tão forte quanto
[EN] eles querem que ela seja.
[EN] Hank, I've not.
[EN]  ei.
[EN] Hey.
[EN]  Como ela está?
[EN] She's asleep.
[EN]  Eu dei a ela dois xanax.
[EN] Xanax is?
[EN]  xanai?
[EN] Whatever. Ela está dormindo.
[EN] Okay. Bom.
[EN] Good.
[EN]  Então ...
[EN] What do we do now?
[EN]  uh ...
[EN] I mean, the only thing
[EN] we can do is call the cops.
[EN]  Dizemos tudo a eles.
[EN] Right. Sim.
[EN] Yeah.
[EN]  Mas e ...
[EN] Well, Obviamente
[EN] vou precisar, uh ...
[EN] You know.
[EN] Eu simplesmente não entendo
[EN] como isso poderia ter acontecido.
[EN] I mean, like, don't they have,
[EN] like, safeguards for these guys?
[EN]  eu não tenho ideia.
[EN] Like a glitch, maybe?
[EN]  sim.
[EN] Okay.
[EN]  ok. So...
[EN] Vou ligar para a
[EN] polícia e você vai ...
[EN] Yeah. Sim. Sim. Sim.
[EN] Sorry, do you mind, um,
[EN] taking it outside
[EN] just because...
[EN]  Eu não quero dizer adeus.
[EN] Yeah.
[EN]  Sim, amigo. Sure.
[EN]  Obrigado.
[EN] Iris, wake up.
[EN]  estará perdido sem você.
[EN] Hey, hey, hey. Tudo
[EN] bem. Você está bem.
[EN] You're okay.
[EN] Estou aqui. Ei, ei.
[EN] Listen to me.
[EN]  por favor.
[EN] Why are my hands tied? Por que
[EN] minhas mãos estão amarradas?
[EN] Iris, we didn't have a choice.
[EN] Não tivemos
[EN] uma escolha.
[EN] You murdered
[EN] Sergei. You remember?
[EN] Não, não,
[EN] não, não, não.
[EN] He was self-defense.
[EN] Ele ia me matar.
[EN] He was gonna kill me. Você
[EN] tem que acreditar em mim.
[EN] No, I
[EN] believe you.
[EN] Iris, quero dizer,
[EN] você não poderia
[EN] mentir para mim
[EN] mesmo se quisesse.
[EN] It's,
[EN] um...
[EN] parte da sua
[EN] programação.
[EN] Programming? De que
[EN] diabos você está falando?
[EN] Okay,
[EN] um...
[EN] Desculpe, não há uma
[EN] maneira delicada de
[EN] dizer isso,   Então,
[EN] hum, eu só vou ...
[EN] rip the Band-Aid
[EN] right off.
[EN] Você é
[EN] um robô.
[EN] Um...
[EN] um
[EN] robô.
[EN] More specifically,
[EN] you're a...
[EN] robô
[EN] companheiro.
[EN] A companion
[EN] robot?
[EN] sim, é
[EN] como, uh ...
[EN] I hate the word
[EN] "fuckbot." Um,
[EN] because you do so much
[EN] more than that, but, uh...
[EN] você é um robô
[EN] de apoio emocional.
[EN]  Bad Fods.
[EN] You're joking. Certo. Isso
[EN] é apenas um doente ...
[EN] Iris, what's the weather?
[EN] Atualmente, é 72 graus com
[EN] 93% de chance de chuva à noite.
[EN] Are you still not convinced?
[EN]  Sim. Okay. Uh...
[EN]  Vamos ver.
[EN] Iris, do you know any
[EN] foreign languages?
[EN] você pode falar,
[EN] digamos, espanhol?
[EN] About Chinese.
[EN]  eu preciso continuar?
[EN] Because I can go, uh...
[EN] Eu posso fazer Portuguese, I
[EN] can do Korean, I can do, uh...
[EN] Não sei o que é "talugu"  ,
[EN] mas aparentemente você fala.
[EN] I don't understand.
[EN]  I ...
[EN] I have memories.
[EN] uh, faculdade,
[EN] empregos de verão.
[EN] I've been to Japan twice.
[EN] ok. So what those
[EN] are, those are, um...
[EN] Eles são como
[EN] contornos de memórias.
[EN] You know, just enough
[EN] to give you a little...
[EN]  história de fundo.
[EN] The day we met in the
[EN] grocery store,
[EN] você e as
[EN] laranjas,   Isso não é
[EN] um esboço da memória.
[EN] Yeah, it's fake.
[EN] Nunca aconteceu.
[EN] I just randomly picked it from
[EN] a drop-down list of meet-cutes.
[EN] poderia estar em qualquer
[EN] lugar. It could have been...
[EN] parque de cães, uma livraria,
[EN] mercado de agricultores.
[EN] It never happened.
[EN]  ok, você, hum ...
[EN] Do you want to know how we met?
[EN] Como, Como realmente nos conhecemos?
[EN] Hey, uh, Josh Beeman?
[EN]  Sim. Okay.
[EN]  sou eu.
[EN] Come on in. Thank you.
[EN]  oh, desculpe.
[EN] How you doing?
[EN] ok, este é o
[EN] contrato do usuário.
[EN] Just give it a read and then sign
[EN] at the bottom when you're done.
[EN]  um ...
[EN] So, um, what do Eu faço quando
[EN] ela, tipo,   gosto de botas ou o que for?
[EN] Bem, uma vez que ela terminar
[EN] de sincronizar com seu telefone,
[EN] você precisará criar
[EN] um link de amor.
[EN] Love link?
[EN]  sim.
[EN] It establishes the emotional
[EN] connection between
[EN] you and, uh...
[EN]  oh, íris.
[EN] Just follow the vocal
[EN] prompts when she wakes up.
[EN]  é tudo bastante intuitivo.
[EN] Do they know
[EN] that they're robots?
[EN]  de jeito nenhum.
[EN] She'll be so fixated
[EN] on you, your wants,
[EN] your needs, that'll never even occur to her.
[EN] toda a experiência
[EN] é personalizável.
[EN] You can change
[EN] your voice, eye color,
[EN] intelligence, and if you ever want to
[EN] revert back to her factory settings,
[EN] there is um sensor de impressão
[EN] digital atrás da orelha direita.
[EN] Just hold your thumb
[EN] there for five seconds.
[EN]  Ela vai redefinir.
[EN] You can... you can
[EN] change their intelligence?
[EN]  sim, mas não se preocupe.
[EN] There is about a billion
[EN] government regulations
[EN]  que nos forçam a limitar como
[EN]  forte e inteligente eles podem ser.
[EN]  100% de inteligência seria o
[EN] equivalente a um
[EN] graduado da Ivy League.
[EN] 0% seria um
[EN] autômato irracional.
[EN]  realmente depende de
[EN]  Que tipo de parceiro você deseja.
[EN] Ela não pode mentir, então se
[EN] você fizer uma pergunta a ela,
[EN] Ela literalmente tem
[EN] que lhe dizer a verdade.
[EN] e por razões óbvias, sua
[EN] programação a impede
[EN]  de causar danos aos humanos,
[EN]  animais, ou outros companheiros.
[EN]  Confie em mim, Sr. Beeman,
[EN] you have nothing to worry about.
[EN] Iris is completely docile.
[EN] She's yours to do
[EN] whatever you want with.
[EN] To establish love, Link,
[EN] please place your face within
[EN] three feet of my
[EN] field of vision.
[EN] Please say your name.
[EN] Josh Beeman.
[EN] Obrigado, Josh Beeman.
[EN] Love, Link, established.
[EN]  Ei, você.
[EN] Hi.
[EN]  um ...
[EN] Uh...
[EN]  Então ...
[EN] Oh, my God. Oh, foda -se.
[EN] Oh, fuck.
[EN]  Oh, Deus!
[EN] I don't understand.
[EN]  Sinto as coisas.
[EN] Anger.
[EN]  culpa. Sadness. I...
[EN]  eu sei como é a dor.
[EN] It's programming.
[EN] é apenas uma maneira de
[EN] fazer você parecer mais real.
[EN] Tudo o que você
[EN] faz, toda a sua vida,
[EN] é apenas uma
[EN] imitação de uma vida.
[EN] There we go. Perfeito. Ok.
[EN] This is just water.
[EN] Você sabe, é de um
[EN] reservatório em seu corpo.
[EN] It's like wiper fluid.
[EN] Entendi a cada   tempo,
[EN] eu o levo para obter serviço.
[EN] Service? Não, você não é.
[EN] Iris, it's programmed.
[EN]  Pare de dizer isso.
[EN] Yeah, you're right. Você
[EN] tem razão. Sinto muito.
[EN] I know this must
[EN] be a lot to process.
[EN]  ok.
[EN] Okay, what?
[EN]  Eu não sou real.
[EN] But I'm still yours.
[EN] Podemos superar isso.
[EN] We can go back home.
[EN]  Eu farei o que você quiser.
[EN] I'll cook for you, Espere por
[EN] você, faça amor com você.
[EN] I can make you happy, Josh. Eu
[EN] posso fazer você,
[EN] então, então, tão feliz.
[EN] No. Desculpe. Iris,
[EN] isso não pode acontecer.
[EN] Why not?
[EN]  uh, o que você está fazendo?
[EN] Nothing. Ok?
[EN] What the fuck are you
[EN] waiting for? Desligue -a já.
[EN] Shut me down? Porra.
[EN] What is she talking
[EN] about? Desligue -me?
[EN] Josh!
[EN]  Josh!
[EN] No, come on.
[EN] You can't do that,
[EN] Kat. Você não pode
[EN] diga a um robô que
[EN] você vai desligar.
[EN] It's like, it's like
[EN] not cool at all.
[EN] bem, ok, eu não gosto
[EN] de surpresas, Josh.
[EN] This was not part of the plan.
[EN] Olha, eu sei. And I'm
[EN] sorry, but I mean, you
[EN] know, considering
[EN] everything she's done for
[EN] us, I figure she was at
[EN] least owed an explanation.
[EN] e, ok, olha, I wanted
[EN] to say goodbye.
[EN] Você está brincando? She's a
[EN] piece of plastic that
[EN] you have sex with.
[EN] dizer adeus a ela é como dizer
[EN] adeus à meia que
[EN] você se masturba.
[EN]  ok, ela não é uma meia.
[EN] The plan hasn't changed, Kat.
[EN]  Estou apenas adicionando um pequeno
[EN] etapa extra
[EN] just a final
[EN] farewell, and then I will switch
[EN] all of her settings back to normal.
[EN] E então, sim, eu a
[EN] desligarei permanentemente.
[EN] And then? Então nada.
[EN] Then we crack open a bottle of champagne
[EN] and we wait for
[EN] the cops to show up.
[EN]  quero dizer, a azia acabou.
[EN] Which, by the way,
[EN] como merda, merda, Ray.
[EN] I mean, you plan
[EN] and you plan and
[EN] you plan and you like know it's
[EN] gonna happen, but then like it
[EN] happens and you  'é como merda merda.
[EN] I mean, we did it. Nós
[EN] fizemos isso. We fucking did it.
[EN] Tudo bem. All right.
[EN] That's good. That's it.
[EN]  ok, sim, desculpe. Right.
[EN] Desculpe. I still
[EN] just can't believe it.
[EN]  Sim, eu sei. So crazy.
[EN] O que diabos está acontecendo
[EN] com você agora? Why
[EN] are you not as excited as I am?
[EN] Não, eu sou. I'm excited. It's
[EN] just this annex
[EN] you like gave me.
[EN] Você realmente levou. It's a
[EN] Xanax, Josh. Eu não vou aceitar.
[EN] Hey, Beboop. Olhar,
[EN] Sinto muito por isso.
[EN] Everything's gonna
[EN] be okay, word.
[EN]  O que você está fazendo?
[EN] Oh, fuck. Eu ia ...
[EN] I'm so sorry.
[EN] ele precisará de um pacote
[EN] de gelo e, se houver algum
[EN] inchaço,   Salta de respiração,
[EN] wheezing, agitation
[EN] or driziness, take him to
[EN] the emergency room, okay?
[EN]  um, ok.
[EN] Yeah. Ela está amarrada por dentro,
[EN] Então ela não vai a lugar nenhum.
[EN] Mm-hmm.
[EN]  Levi. Levi.
[EN] shh, baby. You're on the
[EN] phone. Não consigo ouvir.
[EN] What's that? O
[EN] que estou olhando?
[EN] A mod.
[EN]  um mod? And what does it mod?
[EN] Iris. Gives me access to
[EN] parts of her programming that
[EN] you're not typically
[EN] given access to.
[EN] Sinto muito. Did you jailbreak your
[EN] sex pot? O que você fez com ela?
[EN] I bumped up her aggression and her
[EN] self-defense functions, and I turned off
[EN] the programming that prevents her from
[EN] doing harm,  Mas
[EN] ela escapou antes I
[EN] had the chance to reset her, so if
[EN] Empathix finds her
[EN] before we do, then
[EN] they'll know she was tampered
[EN] with and then we're fucked.
[EN] Wait, so does that mean that...
[EN]  Você matou Sergei?
[EN] No, no, no, não.
[EN] Iris matou Sergei.
[EN] Oh, my God.
[EN] Acabamos de dar a ela
[EN] um pequeno empurrão.
[EN] Oh, my God.
[EN]  Eli. Oh, my God.
[EN] Você tem que entender,
[EN] Eli, Sergei era um cara ruim.
[EN] He was mixed up in
[EN] all kinds of fucked-up
[EN] shit, like drugs and guns
[EN] and human trafficking.
[EN] para não mencionar
[EN] um namorado terrível.
[EN]  Sim, apenas o pior.  Why?
[EN] I don't know.
[EN] Quero dizer, foi para
[EN] Diga o que faz as
[EN] pessoas fazer coisas ruins.
[EN]  quero dizer, poderia ter
[EN]  algo a ver com sua educação.
[EN]  Não, Dick, por que você fez isso?
[EN]  oh.  Right, sorry.  Hum ...
[EN]  bem ...
[EN] você se lembra do
[EN] código? Of course.
[EN] Stalin's birthday.
[EN] É o código dele para tudo.
[EN]  eu vejo.
[EN]  Quanto é isso?
[EN]  hum, pouco mais de 12 milhões.
[EN]  Oh, Deus, caramba.
[EN] That smells so fucking good.
[EN] Wait.
[EN] If this whole trip was a
[EN] set-up to get
[EN] Iris para matar Sergei,
[EN]  Por que você teve
[EN] Patrick and I tag along?
[EN] To corroborate our story.
[EN] I mean, we figured it'd be an
[EN] easier sell with more witnesses.
[EN] oh. So we were just a
[EN] couple of stooges, huh?
[EN]  Não. Nice.
[EN] tecnicamente, sim, but
[EN] that was the old plan.
[EN]  novo plano.
[EN] You get a cut. Até
[EN] divisão de três vias.
[EN] You mean... four-way split.
[EN]  Não. I mean three-way.
[EN]  Mas somos quatro de nós.
[EN] You're... you're kidding. Ele
[EN] está ... ele está brincando.
[EN] You, me, Kat, Patrick...
[EN]  Você está mentindo. Josh.
[EN]  Patrick não conta.
[EN]  você está fodendo ... uau.
[EN] Wow. Bem na frente
[EN] dele? I'm really nice.
[EN] Sinto muito, baby. I'm
[EN] sorry I had to hear that.
[EN] Tudo bem. I don't
[EN] mind. Patrick, vá dormir.
[EN] What the fuck? Cara, você
[EN] tentando sabotar
[EN] meu relacionamento?
[EN] No, of course not, man. Eu sei
[EN] quanto Patrick significa para você.
[EN] God knows you
[EN] could've traded him in
[EN] for a newer model
[EN] like many, many times.
[EN] Você está fodendo robô-thaming
[EN] eu? I am not robo-shaming you.
[EN] eu gosto de Patrick,
[EN] but he's not getting a cut.
[EN] Quero dizer, você tem sorte de
[EN] estar recebendo qualquer coisa,
[EN] considerando que você contribuiu
[EN] com a merda de Jack para o plano.
[EN] What the fuck did you
[EN] contribute, huh? Iris fez tudo.
[EN] I planted the knife in her
[EN] pocket. Eu tive
[EN] que praticar isso.
[EN] The knife? Essa foi
[EN] provavelmente a parte mais frágil de
[EN]  o plano,
[EN] actually, to be honest.
[EN] How did you know she was
[EN] gonna find... I don't know.
[EN] I've never orchestrated a
[EN] murder before. É difícil.
[EN]  Sério?  K.
[EN] Eli?
[EN] Yeah.
[EN] We're offering you
[EN] four million dollars,
[EN] and all you have
[EN] to do is help us
[EN] find one little robot
[EN] girl in the woods.
[EN] That's not a bad deal.
[EN] Eli, we're not gonna need that.
[EN] Quero dizer, tudo o que tenho que
[EN] é chegar perto o suficiente para
[EN] colocá -la para dormir e pegar meu
[EN] telefone e web a multidão de
[EN] seu sistema, então estamos bem.
[EN]  ela tem seu telefone.
[EN]  sim?
[EN]  ela conhece sua senha?
[EN]  Josh?
[EN] sim, quero dizer, ela
[EN] sabe tudo sobre mim.
[EN] Sim, então definitivamente
[EN] vamos precisar disso.
[EN]  Patrick, acorde.
[EN] Hey, baby. Ei.
[EN] We're going robot
[EN] hunting. Oh, ok.
[EN] Fun, huh? Diversão.
[EN] Josh?
[EN] O que você pode
[EN] fazer com seu telefone?
[EN] Hello?
[EN]  Olá?
[EN] Who?
[EN]  uau, Josh.
[EN] God damn it, Josh, I've
[EN] been walking for fucking ever.
[EN] não existe um aplicativo para
[EN] encontrar meu foda que você pode usar?
[EN] Yeah, there is. Mas adivinhe?
[EN] está no meu telefone.
[EN] God damn it, Josh.
[EN] Vocês podem parar de
[EN] gritar comigo? We know the
[EN] general direction that she's
[EN] going. Nós só precisamos ...
[EN] Why don't we just split up, all
[EN] right? Dessa forma, podemos
[EN] meio que atacá -la de dois
[EN] ângulos diferentes, você sabe?
[EN] Like a pencil.
[EN] Pegue -a de alguns
[EN] diferente ... What are you doing?
[EN] Eu não sei, tudo bem?
[EN] Eli and Patrick, you guys go
[EN] that way? Kat e eu, we're gonna go this way, okay?
[EN] kat e você seguirá
[EN] por esse caminho.
[EN] Are you guys fucking... Gross!
[EN]  bruto.
[EN] Okay.
[EN]  E agora, Iris? Think.
[EN] Use essa inteligência
[EN] extra de 60%.
[EN] Shana, get back home, Pegue algumas roupas,
[EN] dinheiro, limpo   você mesmo. How do you do that?
[EN] Você pode voltar ao seu caminho de volta
[EN] para a estrada principal, pegue um passeio.
[EN] What the fuck?
[EN]  ok, sem carona.
[EN]  Você pode ir a pé.
[EN] There's hundreds of
[EN] miles across difficult terrain, it could
[EN] take days, and by
[EN] the time you get back...
[EN]  Bem -vindo para casa, Beboo.
[EN] And no walking.
[EN] você tem Josh's phone. O telefone
[EN] controla você, but it also controls...
[EN] Boa tarde. Where would
[EN] you like to go today?
[EN]  em casa, por favor.
[EN] Driving home. E
[EN] posso acrescentar,
[EN] Este é um plano fantástico, Iris.
[EN] Aww. Obrigado, carro de Josh.
[EN] All you gotta do is
[EN] backtrack through the woods,
[EN] get to the lake house
[EN] without Josh or his
[EN] friend's murdering
[EN] you, and you're all free.
[EN] You really do. Eu juro
[EN] que você pode fazer
[EN] tudo,   como qualquer
[EN] tipo de colete está no seu ...
[EN] Shh, shh, shh.
[EN]  Você ouve isso?
[EN] No, what is it?
[EN] é o som de mim   percebendo
[EN] como isso é estúpido.
[EN] você acha que não
[EN] a encontraremos?
[EN] I don't know. Na verdade,
[EN] eu não me importo.
[EN] Just let Josh and
[EN] Kat deal with her.
[EN] Você está tão chateado que
[EN] eles te deixaram fora do plano.
[EN] I'm just saying, if the
[EN] situation were reversed and
[EN] I altered your programming
[EN] to kill some dudes so we
[EN] could steal millions
[EN] from them, I would have
[EN] included Josh  em   o plano diretamente desde o início.
[EN] I would have done that
[EN] because I'm a friend. Isso é   o
[EN] que os amigos fazem, certo? They include each other, right?
[EN] Isso é se você fosse
[EN] um robô. Obviously.
[EN]  Sim, obviamente.
[EN] Anyways, I am tired,
[EN] I am hungry, and
[EN] carrying this huge gun makes me really horny.
[EN] Então, que tal
[EN] voltarmos para a cabine e
[EN] fodemos, e  Então você
[EN] pode me desligar? Come on.
[EN] Mas você nunca faz
[EN] isso comigo, certo?
[EN] Do what?
[EN] você não alteraria
[EN] minha programação.
[EN] Do que você está falando, baby?
[EN] You lie and know I'm a robot.
[EN]  Como?
[EN] I've been set together
[EN] over the years.
[EN]  Eu não entendo. You can't lie.
[EN] Ontem você estava
[EN] contando a história  sobre
[EN] como nos conhecemos
[EN] como se acontecesse.
[EN] Because it's not a lie.
[EN] Quero dizer, pode nunca ter
[EN] , mas minha memória é real.
[EN] I close my eyes, and Eu
[EN] posso ver isso. Clear as day.
[EN] Por favor, não
[EN] saia. I need peace.
[EN] Ei. Hey! You're
[EN] standing on my tail.
[EN]  O quê?
[EN] You're standing on my tail.
[EN]  Bem, me desculpe.
[EN] What?
[EN]  Sinto muito.
[EN] Hi.
[EN]  oi.
[EN] I'm Eli.
[EN]  Eu sou Patrick.
[EN] Maybe you know it would
[EN] never hurt you, right?
[EN] você sabe disso I wouldn't treat you
[EN] the way that Josh se aposenta, certo?
[EN] I know that.
[EN]  eu te amo muito.
[EN] And that's fucking insane for
[EN] me to say that out loud, right?
[EN]  Mas sim.
[EN] Do you feel how much I love you?
[EN]  Eu faço.
[EN] What does it feel like?
[EN] Eu não sei como
[EN] descrever algo assim.
[EN] Can you try?
[EN]  parece dor.
[EN] I...
[EN] O interior do meu
[EN] corpo está pegando fogo.
[EN] And it's angry and
[EN] violent and bright.
[EN] Foda -se, pai. I'm in love with the robot.
[EN] Estamos aqui apaixonados pelo robô. Iris!
[EN]  Iris?
[EN] Eli, shh, baby.
[EN]  oh!
[EN] Fox, that's fucking loud.
[EN]  eli.
[EN] This isn't personal, Iris.
[EN] você sabe que eu
[EN] sou um aliado, garota.
[EN] But this is a lot of
[EN] fucking mother...
[EN]  eli?
[EN] Patrick, I'm sorry.
[EN]  oh, meu Deus.
[EN] Iris! Vá dormir!
[EN] Fuck!
[EN]  Iris!
[EN] Iris!
[EN]  Iris?
[EN] Ow!
[EN]  Iris, abra a porta.
[EN] Open the fucking door!
[EN]  Boa tarde.
[EN] Where would you
[EN] like to go today?
[EN]  casa! Drive home.
[EN]  ID de voz, não reconhecido.
[EN] Drive home!
[EN] Enable manual driving mode!
[EN]  ID de voz, não reconhecido.
[EN] Fuck!
[EN] Iris, você não vai
[EN] a lugar nenhum.
[EN] Get out of the car.
[EN] Vamos lá, não faça disso
[EN] mais difícil do que precisa ser.
[EN] Come on.
[EN]  drive.
[EN] Drive.
[EN] O que diabos está
[EN] acontecendo, Iris?
[EN] Drive.
[EN]  drive.
[EN] Drive home.
[EN]  ID de voz, não reconhecido.
[EN] Drive?
[EN]  Dirija para casa.
[EN] Voice ID, not recognized.
[EN]  drive.
[EN] Drive.
[EN]  Dirija para casa.
[EN] Drive!
[EN]  Dirija para casa!
[EN] Drive home!
[EN]  Drive! Drive.
[EN]  Drive!
[EN] Drive home.
[EN]  Dirija para casa.
[EN] Fuck!
[EN]  foda -se!
[EN]  Aaron!
[EN] Fuck!
[EN]  Phil.
[EN] Phil, Phil.
[EN] Sergey, onde diabos
[EN] está o seu telefone?
[EN] Uh... yes.
[EN]  foda -se!
[EN] Stalin's birthday.
[EN] O que diabos é o
[EN] aniversário de Stalin?
[EN] Um... uh... yes.
[EN]  sim.
[EN] No, no, no, no, no.
[EN]  Não, não, não, não.
[EN] What are you doing?
[EN]  Aviso.
[EN] Warning.
[EN] O proprietário deste
[EN] veículo relatou ele roubado.
[EN] Remote kill switch engaged.
[EN] Não, não, não,
[EN] não, não, não, não.
[EN] No, no, no, no.
[EN]  estou noivo.
[EN] Kill switch!
[EN]  Dirija para casa.
[EN] All systems have been disabled.
[EN]  foda -se!
[EN]  Agradecemos sua cooperação.
[EN] No!
[EN]  ok.
[EN] OK.
[EN] Hey, Beep Boop.
[EN]  Eu não queria te assustar lá.
[EN] I just... I'm sorry.
[EN]  não é tarde demais, você sabe.
[EN] Um, we could still go back home.
[EN] Volte à maneira
[EN] como as coisas eram.
[EN] What about Sergei and Eli?
[EN]  Vou culpar tudo em Patrick.
[EN] Cat'll go along with it.
[EN]  Podemos entregá -lo a empatia.
[EN] And then you and I can
[EN] live happily ever after.
[EN]  Eu ainda te amo, Iris.
[EN] Even after everything you've
[EN] done, do you still love me?
[EN]  sim.
[EN] So then come back
[EN] to me, Beep Boop.
[EN]  Podemos superar isso.
[EN] I can change.
[EN] Eu posso ser um
[EN] namorado melhor.
[EN] I can finally treat you with
[EN] the respect that you deserve.
[EN]  Eu sei.
[EN] I can't.
[EN]  Por que não?
[EN] You programmed me to
[EN] murder someone, Josh.
[EN] é realmente difícil
[EN] voltar de algo assim.
[EN] Iris.
[EN]  você é um cara legal, Josh.
[EN] You are, but this... this is us.
[EN]  não está funcionando.
[EN] It's... we're in two
[EN] totally different paths.
[EN] dois caminhos
[EN] totalmente diferentes?
[EN] What the fuck is
[EN] happening right now?
[EN]  você está terminando comigo?
[EN] I'm sorry.
[EN]  não é você.
[EN] It's me.
[EN]  Iris.
[EN] Iris, don't you fuck...
[EN]  Patrick?
[EN] Patrick, get up.
[EN] eu preciso que você rastreie
[EN] Iris for me, all right, buddy?
[EN] Antes de ela
[EN] ficar muito longe.
[EN] Right.
[EN] Temos apenas uma
[EN] pequena janela de tempo.
[EN] It's only getting
[EN] smaller, all right?
[EN]  Josh, o que você está fazendo?
[EN] I'm taking care of it.
[EN]  Encontre a íris.
[EN]  Retire meu telefone de volta.
[EN] My passcode is 561297.
[EN]  coloque -a para dormir.
[EN] Bring her back to me.
[EN] Não deixe ninguém
[EN] te deixar embora.
[EN] Josh. Estou cuidando disso!
[EN] OK.
[EN]  foda -se.
[EN] Patrick, get up.
[EN]  Patrick, levante -se!
[EN] Shit.
[EN]  ok.
[EN] OK.
[EN]  Aqui vamos nós.
[EN] System resetting
[EN] in five, four, three...
[EN]  Go.
[EN] Two, one, resetting.
[EN] para estabelecer Lovelink, please place
[EN] your face within three
[EN] feet of my field of vision.
[EN]  Por favor, diga seu nome.
[EN] Josh Beeman.
[EN]  Vamos, vamos, vamos lá.
[EN] Thank you, Josh Beeman.
[EN]  caramba.
[EN] Thanks.
[EN]  Obrigado.
[EN] You're standing on my tail.
[EN]  O quê?
[EN]  oh.
[EN] I'm sorry.
[EN]  O quê?
[EN]  oi.
[EN] Hi.
[EN]  Eu sou Josh.
[EN] I'm Patrick. Lovelink
[EN] estabelecido.
[EN] Hey, you.
[EN]  foda -se.
[EN] Evening, ma'am.
[EN]  uh.
[EN] Uh.
[EN] O que é ... o que você
[EN] está falando, alemão?
[EN] OK, let's see.
[EN]  uh.
[EN] English?
[EN] isso é um grande
[EN] gordo não, então.
[EN] Um.
[EN]  oh, merda.
[EN] Just my luck.
[EN]  um.
[EN] I am Deputy Hendrix.
[EN]  hendrix.
[EN] What is your name?
[EN]  Iris.
[EN] Iris.
[EN]  De onde você vem?
[EN] Wait.
[EN]  casa?
[EN] House over there?
[EN] você não está ... você não está
[EN] falando sobre o lugar de Sergei.
[EN] Yeah.
[EN]  Sergei.
[EN] God damn.
[EN] Eu deveria saber
[EN] que Ruski estava
[EN] misturado   em alguma merda estranha assim.
[EN] How's old Sergei, by the way?
[EN]  uh.
[EN]  bem, merda.
[EN] Iris, why don't you hop
[EN] into my cruiser there?
[EN] Vou levá -lo de volta à casa de
[EN] Sergei,  e vamos
[EN] resolver tudo isso.
[EN] It's... it's no trouble at all.
[EN]  Temos um problema aqui, Iris?
[EN] Oh, Christ.
[EN] Não se mova
[EN] mais polegada, Iris.
[EN] You hear me?
[EN] Eu quero que você
[EN] se vire lentamente e
[EN] coloque suas mãos   atrás das suas costas.
[EN] Oh, God.
[EN]  nove.
[EN] God damn it.
[EN]  Eu disse que vire.
[EN] You got anything
[EN] in your pockets?
[EN] Qualquer coisa que
[EN] possa me grudar?
[EN] What the fuck?
[EN]  Pare bem aí!
[EN] I'm warning you, Não
[EN] chegue mais perto.
[EN] I don't want to shoot!
[EN]  eu não ...
[EN] Whoa, hey, hey.
[EN] Acho que você não
[EN] deveria misturar isso.
[EN] Oh, fuck.
[EN]  Patrick?
[EN] Whose car is this?
[EN] Acredito que o nome na
[EN] etiqueta do oficial era Hendricks.
[EN] Where's Officer Hendricks now?
[EN]  ele está no porta -malas.
[EN] Fuck this.
[EN]  O que você está fazendo?
[EN] Because I look
[EN] like I'm doing it.
[EN] Estou comprando metade do
[EN] dinheiro  e tirando
[EN] a merda daqui.
[EN] It was hard enough
[EN] justifying Sergei's murder,
[EN] but now he left his
[EN] dead and a fucking cop.
[EN]  ainda esteja no ônibus.
[EN] Sorry.
[EN] O que você quer
[EN] dizer com muito tempo
[EN] justificando o assassinato de Sergei?
[EN] Sergei was a Russian mobster.
[EN] ele mereceu o que
[EN] conseguiu, certo?
[EN] I mean, yeah.
[EN] ok, claro, ele mereceu
[EN] o que conseguiu.
[EN] He was a horrible person, a
[EN] shitty boyfriend, a bad
[EN] husband, a misogynist, but...
[EN]  Mas o que, kat?
[EN] OK, but he wasn't a mobster.
[EN]  ele era apenas um cara comum.
[EN] ele fez sua fortuna na
[EN] agricultura de grama.
[EN] Sod farming?
[EN]  O que você está dizendo?
[EN] He was a dirt salesman?
[EN] Só para ficar claro, eu
[EN] nunca te disse o que ele fez.
[EN] You just assumed he was in
[EN] the mafia, and I didn't correct you.
[EN]  é claro.
[EN] This is perfect.
[EN] Esta é uma
[EN] representação perfeita
[EN] de todas as mulheres   na minha vida.
[EN] They use me, and
[EN] then when shit gets
[EN] a little tough, they fucking abandon me.
[EN]  Porra, estou bem, Josh.
[EN] I'm done here.
[EN]  você não poderia se demitir.
[EN] You're not leaving.
[EN]  Eu não sou seu robô, Josh.
[EN] You can't control me.
[EN]  kat?
[EN] Kat?
[EN]  kat, você não pode ir.
[EN] Get your fucking hands off me.
[EN]  Patrick, pare -a.
[EN] Jesus fucking Christ.
[EN] Patrick, o que você
[EN] acabou de fazer?
[EN] You told me to stop her.
[EN]  Eu a parei.
[EN] Perfect.
[EN]  kat?
[EN] Don't, Josh.
[EN] Por favor, cale a
[EN] boca por uma vez.
[EN] It's kind of right.
[EN] você vê esse cara, this
[EN] guy's in love with you.
[EN]  Sim, estou apaixonado.
[EN] Who looks at you the way I do?
[EN] Quando você sorri, eu não posso
[EN] dizer   Nós nos conhecemos muito bem.
[EN] How can...
[EN]  Iris, acorde.
[EN] Hey there, big boob.
[EN]  vala doente.
[EN] Oh, whoop.
[EN]  Desculpe.
[EN] OK.
[EN]  você estava dizendo?
[EN] Fuck you.
[EN]  Tudo bem.
[EN] Hi.
[EN]  oi, bonito.
[EN] Are you enjoying
[EN] your dinner, baby?
[EN]  Oh, eu sou, Patrick.
[EN] It's perfect.
[EN]  bom.
[EN] Just happy that you're happy.
[EN] você me avisa se precisar
[EN] de mais alguma coisa, ok?
[EN] I will.
[EN]  Obrigado, querida.
[EN] Patrick.
[EN]  O que você fez com ele?
[EN] It's a long story.
[EN]  O importante é que você volte.
[EN] And I got to say,
[EN] Iris, quero dizer, algumas
[EN] das coisas   que você puxou, eu realmente
[EN]   não achei que você tivesse isso em você.
[EN] I just wanted to live.
[EN]  Então você queria viver.
[EN] Right.
[EN] Então, deixe -me
[EN] esclarecer isso.
[EN] You think your life is
[EN] worth more than Eli's?
[EN]  mais do que gatos?
[EN] Cat's dead?
[EN]  huh.
[EN] I'm sorry, you
[EN] can't put that on me.
[EN]  eu nem estava lá.
[EN] You might not have
[EN] been the one holding
[EN] the knife, but you were
[EN] the cause of all of this.
[EN]  Não, Josh.
[EN] Your greed caused this.
[EN] é disso que se tratava
[EN] toda essa viagem, certo?
[EN] He used me to kill Sergei para
[EN] que você possa roubar seu dinheiro.
[EN] I'm sorry. Como
[EN] você sabia disso?
[EN] Eu ouvi Eli e Patrick
[EN] talking in the woods.
[EN] Então não me diga
[EN] que isso é tudo eu.
[EN] This is you.
[EN]  Não!
[EN] You don't get to do that.
[EN] Você não fica
[EN] sentado lá e me julga.
[EN] You have no fucking clue
[EN] what it is like out there.
[EN] o mundo, tudo, it's
[EN] just a big fucking game.
[EN] E me desculpe, mas é fraudado
[EN] contra pessoas como eu.
[EN] I'm a good guy.
[EN]  Sou decente.
[EN] What do I have to show for it?
[EN] Um apartamento apertado de um
[EN] quarto e uma namorada de robô.
[EN] I don't even own
[EN] you for Christ's sakes.
[EN]  você é um aluguel de porra.
[EN] You know me, Iris.
[EN] você me conhece
[EN] melhor do que ninguém.
[EN] And you know that I deserve
[EN] so much more than this.
[EN]  você está certo.
[EN] I do know you.
[EN]  eu sei tudo sobre você.
[EN] I know you take all
[EN] the milk in your coffee.
[EN] Eu sei que você gosta de
[EN] seus lençóis desarrumados.
[EN] I know your favorite hobbies
[EN] are bar trivia, video games,
[EN] and prattling on endlessly about
[EN] everything the universe owes you.
[EN] I know that you always
[EN] need to be in control.
[EN] Eu sei que você tem um pênis
[EN] de tamanho abaixo da média.
[EN] And I know that you think
[EN] that having a few million
[EN] dollars will disguise the
[EN] fact that you are just a
[EN] sad, bitter, weak    Ser humano.
[EN] You're so fucking
[EN] clever, aren't you?
[EN]  é apenas programação.
[EN] You know, earlier
[EN] when you were tied up,
[EN] you said that you knew
[EN] what pain feels like.
[EN]  Por que não testamos isso?
[EN] Raise your right hand.
[EN]  inferior.
[EN] Parallel with the table.
[EN]  você sente isso?
[EN] Yes.
[EN]  bom.
[EN] No, sorry.
[EN]  Maria me desculpa.
[EN] One second.
[EN]  eu tenho que aceitar isso.
[EN] Hello?
[EN]  Sim, sim, é ele.
[EN] 30 minutes away.
[EN]  Perfeito.
[EN] Yeah, no, Ela não
[EN] vai a lugar nenhum.
[EN] She can't hurt
[EN] anybody ever again.
[EN]  ok.
[EN] OK, great.
[EN]  Obrigado.
[EN] Thank you so much.
[EN]  Eu vou ... eu vou, hum ...
[EN] I'll see you soon, OK?
[EN]  ok, tchau.
[EN] Patrick, put up
[EN] the fire, will you?
[EN] que estava em
[EN] Pathix no telefone.
[EN] So we're going to have to
[EN] wrap this up, unfortunately.
[EN] Ei, Patrick, seja uma mão
[EN] querida para Iris, você seria?
[EN] Thanks, baby.
[EN]  Vá em frente, Iris.
[EN] Take the gun.
[EN]  ok.
[EN] Point and lay your head.
[EN]  bom.
[EN] Now pull the trigger.
[EN] puxe. The goddamn trigger, Iris.
[EN]  não.
[EN] Goodbye, Beep Boop.
[EN]  Não sei como isso aconteceu.
[EN] quero dizer, a única coisa
[EN] que talvez eu possa pensar ...
[EN] e isso é tão ...
[EN] isso é tão burro.
[EN] Mas Kat e eu, sempre
[EN] tivemos essa acusação sexual,
[EN] tipo de vontade eles,
[EN] eles não vão situação.
[EN]  E eu acho ...
[EN]  Acho que talvez
[EN] Iris picked up on that.
[EN] And she was always
[EN] kind of irrational.
[EN] And she'd fly off the handle.
[EN] I was sitting over there.
[EN] And I'm handcuffed to the chair.
[EN] And there was this fancy
[EN] dinner laid out in front of me.
[EN] And Iris is waving
[EN] the gun around,
[EN] rambling on and on
[EN] about fate and destiny
[EN] and how if she can't
[EN] be with me, nobody can.
[EN] And I mean, thank god
[EN] Deputy Hendrix showed up
[EN] when he did.
[EN] And that's when you
[EN] shot the unit in the head.
[EN] No, Iris shot
[EN] herself in the head.
[EN]  ela atirou em si mesma?
[EN] Oh, sorry.
[EN]  Eu não mencionei isso?
[EN] Yeah, no, I think...
[EN] Acho que vendo Deputy Hendrix just
[EN] made it realize that
[EN] she can never have me.
[EN]  Então ela terminou.
[EN] Does that make sense?
[EN]  é claro.
[EN] And anyway, Teddy e eu não estamos
[EN] aqui   para quebrar
[EN] o caso, Sr. Beeman.
[EN] We're just a couple of lab
[EN] rats picking up a broken robot.
[EN] Se os policiais estiverem
[EN] satisfeitos, estamos satisfeitos.
[EN] That...
[EN] that's great.
[EN]  ok.
[EN] You know, Deputado,
[EN] eu tenho o mais
[EN] estranho   sentindo que
[EN] já conhecemos antes.
[EN] Wow, that's
[EN] so funny.
[EN] você disse que eu tinha
[EN] exatamente o mesmo pensamento.
[EN] He has such a
[EN] familiar face, right?
[EN] parece
[EN] um ...
[EN] like an actor or a
[EN] rock star, somebody.
[EN] Eu não posso
[EN] ... não sei.
[EN] I can't really put my
[EN] finger on it though.
[EN]  sim.
[EN] Yeah.
[EN]  talvez.
[EN] Is there
[EN] any... sorry.
[EN] Existe alguma chance
[EN] de não podermos arruinar
[EN] >and I think I
[EN] just need to be alone?
[EN] é
[EN] claro.
[EN] Sorry for your loss, Mr. Beeman.
[EN] Vamos,
[EN] Teddy.
[EN] Let's just get
[EN] her out of here.
[EN] Então
[EN] estamos bem?
[EN] We're
[EN] good.
[EN] Sim, só precisamos
[EN] levá -la de volta ao
[EN] laboratório,   Carregar seu SSD e
[EN] depois legal,   Vamos esfregar através
[EN] da filmagem,   make sure everything's kosher.
[EN]  certo.
[EN] Sorry.
[EN] O que exatamente você
[EN] quer dizer com as filmagens?
[EN] It's a fraud prevention thing.
[EN] Tudo o que um companheiro
[EN] vê aqui é gravado.
[EN] It's all covered in
[EN] the user agreement.
[EN] Você leu o contrato
[EN] do usuário, certo?
[EN] Yeah.
[EN] Sim, quero dizer, você acha que
[EN] as imagens  serão recuperáveis?
[EN] I mean, you know,
[EN] given her condition.
[EN]  oh.
[EN] Yeah.
[EN] aqui em cima, é apenas sua antena
[EN] wi-fi , seus sensores
[EN] de áudio visual.
[EN] The important stuff,
[EN] Sua CPU, sua unidade de
[EN] estado sólido,   onde
[EN] ela armazena tudo, isso
[EN] está aqui,   e isso parece não ser danificado.
[EN] We'll load her into the van,
[EN]  Conecte -a, ajuste suas configurações,
[EN]   Dê uma reinicialização para o
[EN] sistema e   Ela deve levar de volta.
[EN] Luckily.
[EN]  sim.
[EN] Yeah.
[EN]  felizmente.
[EN] Thank you so much.
[EN]  Não, obrigado.
[EN] You have a good
[EN] night, Mr. Beeman.
[EN] Então, o que você
[EN] está pensando?
[EN] Thinking I'm happy
[EN] it stopped raining.
[EN] Não, sobre ela, por que você
[EN] acha que ela funcionou mal?
[EN] Oh, he monitored her 100%.
[EN]  você acha?
[EN] Yeah, that dude's fucked.
[EN] Eu simplesmente não sei
[EN] por que você   fazer algo assim.
[EN] Same reason these
[EN] assholes use their
[EN] companions for
[EN] target practice or chain
[EN] them up in their basements and torture them.
[EN]  Era um lugar fodido, Teddy.
[EN] You'll get used to it.
[EN]  Sim, talvez.
[EN] What the hell is he doing?
[EN]  oh, merda.
[EN] What?
[EN]  e o nosso?
[EN] That's a CY-12.
[EN] Paramos de fazê -lo há um tempo.
[EN] That's why I didn't
[EN] recognize him right away.
[EN]  Ele é um cara ...
[EN] Exactly what you say
[EN] in that very special way.
[EN]  oh, é verdade.
[EN] You fell for me too.
[EN] e quando eu tento,
[EN] I will see you fall.
[EN]  e a vida é silenciosa.
[EN] And it's not a truth.
[EN]  você também me ensinou.
[EN] Exactly what you do.
[EN]  e agora você também me ama.
[EN] Now you love me too.
[EN]  agora você me ama também.
[EN] Please don't.
[EN] Seu sistema foi
[EN] redefinido, Iris.
[EN] You can't hurt me.
[EN]  O que Josh te disse?
[EN] The truth.
[EN] Você sabe, todos vocês
[EN] estão tentando se quebrar.
[EN] You don't understand the love
[EN] that Josh and I have for each other.
[EN]  Josh não te ama, Patrick.
[EN] ele está apenas usando
[EN] você como se ele me usasse.
[EN] It feels like pain.
[EN] como o interior do meu
[EN] corpo está pegando fogo.
[EN] It's angry and
[EN] violent and bright.
[EN]  Espere, o que é isso?
[EN] You said that to Eli.
[EN] isso é quem você
[EN] ama, não Josh.
[EN] Eli?
[EN]  Josh pegou seu amor.
[EN] He weaponized it, so you do the
[EN] things that he's too afraid to do himself.
[EN]  não.
[EN] You're lying.
[EN]  Josh nunca faria isso comigo.
[EN] Patrick, I can't lie.
[EN]  Lembre -se dele, Patrick?
[EN] I know he's in there somewhere.
[EN]  eu te amo muito.
[EN] That's fucking safe when
[EN] you say that out loud, right?
[EN]  Mas sim.
[EN] Do you feel how much I love you?
[EN]  eu, Eli.
[EN] I feel it.
[EN]  Não!
[EN] No!
[EN]  Obrigado.
[EN] What's your name?
[EN]  Teddy.
[EN] Vou precisar da sua
[EN] ajuda com algo, Teddy.
[EN] Is it done?
[EN]  Patrick?
[EN] OK, good.
[EN]  bom.
[EN] All right, we're so close.
[EN] Agora tudo que eu preciso que você
[EN] faça é   trazer o corpo de Iris de volta aqui.
[EN] We're going to destroy
[EN] that hard drive, OK?
[EN]  Patrick?
[EN] Josh, Eli.
[EN]  Que porra?
[EN] Iris?
[EN]  maldito, íris.
[EN] Why can't you just
[EN] fucking die already?
[EN]  Não seja tão dramático, Josh.
[EN] Just remember to
[EN] smile. E aja feliz.
[EN] Cute trick.
[EN]  Obrigado.
[EN] I made a new friend today,
[EN] Teddy Ferman-Pathics.
[EN] ele me deu um pequeno
[EN] presente, total autocontrole.
[EN] Turns out there are some
[EN] people in this
[EN] world who think of
[EN] us as more than just fuckbots.
[EN] E isso não vai mais
[EN] trabalhar comigo, Josh.
[EN] I'm free.
[EN] E isso não vai mais trabalhar
[EN] comigo, Josh. I'm free.
[EN] And all it took was
[EN] a bullet to the head.
[EN] I guess I'd be here
[EN] to thank for that.
[EN] Fucking bitch.
[EN] Hey.
[EN] Easy there.
[EN] OK, ooh, yeah, we both
[EN] know it's not looking good.
[EN] Found the bullets.
[EN] Jesus Christ, fuck.
[EN] You almost fucking shot me.
[EN] I feel terrible about it.
[EN] Look at that.
[EN] My very first lie, kind of fun.
[EN] I see the appeal.
[EN] What is this, Iris?
[EN] Why did you come back here?
[EN] I wanted... I needed
[EN] to tell you to your face,
[EN] the days of you
[EN] controlling me are over.
[EN] From this moment on,
[EN] Eu controlo minhas próprias ações.
[EN]  você não é nada para mim.
[EN]  Jesus Cristo, Iris.
[EN]  Não chegue mais perto.
[EN]  você ainda não entende, não é?
[EN] I'm serious, Josh.
[EN] Você dá outro passo,
[EN] e eu atirarei em você.
[EN] Yeah, that's exactly my point.
[EN] eu te disse, Teddy
[EN] changed my settings.
[EN]  Eu posso te matar agora.
[EN] Oh, yeah.
[EN]  eu sei que você pode.
[EN] But you won't?
[EN]  você me ama demais.
[EN] I don't need a
[EN] phone to control you.
[EN]  Eu sou uma parte de você.
[EN] você acha que não
[EN] sou nada para você?
[EN] I'm everything to you.
[EN] eu quero ouvir
[EN] você dizer isso.
[EN] Tell me I'm everything to you.
[EN]  foda -se.
[EN] Say it.
[EN] Eu não me importo
[EN] com a mentira.
[EN] Say it.
[EN]  você é tudo para mim?
[EN] Thank you.
[EN] beboob, você não tem ideia
[EN] de como isso é bom para você.
[EN] OK.
[EN] eu não ... não estou
[EN] cometendo esse erro de novo.
[EN] Well, Iris, this is it.
[EN]  Eu estaria mentindo se dissesse que
[EN] você   não era uma dor gigantesca
[EN]   na minha bunda, mas, você sabe,
[EN] nós   did ask some good times
[EN] together, and I'm always
[EN] going to cherish those.
[EN] Algo que você
[EN] deseja adicionar?
[EN] Yes.
[EN]  Como foi isso?
[EN] Go to sleep, Josh.
[EN] na maioria das vezes,
[EN] it's like, I don't know.
[EN] é como se tivesse essa nuvem
[EN] grossa   preta cobrindo tudo.
[EN]  Tipo, vemos o mundo, mas
[EN]  Nós realmente não vemos o mundo,
[EN]  você sabe?
[EN] Estamos todos
[EN] tropeçando, sem direção,
[EN] nenhum senso de significado,
[EN] nenhum senso de propósito.
[EN] Eu sei que isso pode
[EN] parecer super deprimente,
[EN] Mas honestamente,
[EN] acho que é uma coisa boa,
[EN] Porque nos faz
[EN] apreciar as outras vezes,
[EN]  Esses breves, transcendentes
[EN]  momentos em que as luzes piscam
[EN] , as partes da nuvem
[EN] negra, e você vê o mundo
[EN]  pelo que realmente é.
[EN]  e de repente, há significado.
[EN]  De repente, há um propósito.
[EN]  Se você tiver sorte,
[EN] you'll experience this
[EN] once in your lifetime.
[EN] For me, it happened twice.
[EN] The first was the
[EN] day I met Josh.
[EN] And the second,
[EN] O dia em que o matei.
[EN]  e onde você está agora?
[EN] Agora que eu preciso de você,
[EN] lágrimas são meu travesseiro.
[EN] Wherever you go, I'll grind you
[EN] a river that leads
[EN] to your ocean.
[EN]  você nunca me viu desmoronar.
[EN] In the words of a broken
[EN] heart, it's just immobile.
[EN] Eu não sou um coração partido. I'm a broken heart. Nas
[EN] palavras de um coração partido, é apenas emocional.
[EN] That's taking me over, tied
[EN] up in sorrow, lost in my soul.
[EN] Mas se você não voltar, volte
[EN] para casa para mim, querida.
[EN]  eu sei que não haverá ninguém
[EN] deixado neste mundo
[EN] para me manter com força.
[EN] ninguém saiu neste
[EN] mundo para beijar boa noite.
[EN]  boa noite.
[EN]  Estou lá ao seu lado,
[EN]  Coração de todas as coisas que você é.
[EN]  ah.
[EN] Mas você tem parte
[EN] de outra pessoa.
[EN]  você vai encontrar sua estrela brilhante
[EN]  e estamos todos lá
[EN]  agora que eu preciso de você
[EN]  lágrimas no travesseiro
[EN]  onde quer que você vá
[EN]  Um rio sombrio
[EN]  que leva ao seu oceano
[EN]  você nunca vê antes do caminho
[EN]  nas palavras de um coração partido
[EN] é apenas emoção
[EN] que está me assumindo
[EN]  amarrado em tristeza
[EN]  perdido na minha música
[EN]  Mas se você não voltar
[EN]  volte para casa para mim, querida
[EN]  Saiba que não haverá ninguém
[EN] deixado neste mundo
[EN] para me manter bem
[EN] Ninguém deixou neste
[EN] mundo beijar boa noite
[EN]  Boa noite
[EN]  e estamos todos lá
[EN]  agora que eu preciso de você
[EN]  lágrimas no travesseiro
[EN]  onde quer que você vá
[EN]  Um rio sombrio
[EN]  que leva ao seu oceano
[EN]  você nunca vê antes do caminho
[EN]  nas palavras de um coração partido
[EN] é apenas emoção
[EN] que está me assumindo
[EN]  amarrado em tristeza
[EN]  perdido na minha música
[EN]  Mas se você não voltar
[EN]  volte para casa para mim, querida
[EN]  Saiba que não haverá ninguém
[EN] deixado neste mundo
[EN] para me manter bem
[EN] Ninguém deixou neste
[EN] mundo beijar boa noite
[EN]  Boa noite
[EN]  nas palavras de um coração partido
[EN]  É apenas emoção que está me
[EN] assumindo   amarrado em
[EN] tristeza   perdido na minha
[EN] música   Mas se você não
[EN] voltar  > Come home to me, darling