Sentido!
Pegue seu kit de caça. Vamos sair às 07h00.
Essa vista nunca envelhece, não é?
Não importa quantas vezes você veja.
Ah, não chegue perto daquilo.
São cogumelos venenosos. O nome não é à toa.
Se comer um desses, você vai acabar no necrotério rapidinho
a menos que alguém tenha um fígado novinho
dando sopa pra você.
Blake. Blake.
Blake.
Você ouviu o que eu disse?
Sim, senhor.
O que eu disse?
Não coma os cogumelos.
Como eles se chamam?
Uh...
See, this is what I'm talking about-- you're not hearing me.
Você está perdido no seu próprio mundo.
Este lugar é lindo. Mas também é perigoso.
Você pode sobreviver se souber exatamente o que fazer.
Sim, senhor.
People get taken from you-- -- like that.
Não é difícil morrer.
É a coisa mais fácil do mundo.
We are all...
inches away from it.
And I'm not always gonna be around to watch over you,
but I'm gonna make damn sure that you know
how to survive as...
Blake.
You know you need to stay near me.
Right fucking next to me, boy!
If you don't do what I say, you get hurt.
Do you want to get hurt?! Huh?
Do you want to get hurt?!
No, sir, I don't. I just...
I wanted to get a better shot at the deer.
Get up in that deer blind.
Now.
Cover your ears.
What was it, Dad?
A bear.
They're all over this side of the valley.
Pick yourself up, and let's go
while there's still some light left.
Kiel 714, this is Lovell 819.
Kiel 714, this is Lovell 819. Do you read me?
Where in the hell are you, Dan?
DAN What is it, Grady?
Dan.
I saw it.
Saw what?
You know what I'm talking about.
That hiker?
The face of the wolf?
Dan, it's real.
I had it in my scope.
I almost shot it.
Grady, what is the point
in going up that mountain after dark
looking for something that doesn't want to be found?
I wasn't looking for it.
I was hunting deer down by the river.
And it came after my boy.
I'm gonna get it, Dan.
And you got to come with me.
Don't you want to keep your boy safe?
Can we get some ice cream?
Please? Please, please, please, please, please, please...
I got you a hot chocolate at the museum.
That's not a dessert.
That's a drink.
Oh, I think it's dessert, missy.
Well, did you know you're the best dad in the whole world?
Yeah, I'm sure the timing of that
has nothing to do with the ice cream.
It doesn't. I just wanted to tell you.
I'm serious.
Eh, this feels very transactional.
I don't know what that means.
Hey, get down.
Ginger.
Get down right now.
Okay, that's it, no ice cream
in three, two, one.
No, the dog don't jump off the motherfucking leash!
Hey, hey, hey.
I told you to get down.
Why didn't you listen to me, damn it?
Why didn't you listen to me?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I lost my temper.
That's not me.
I don't want to be like that.
I just need you to listen when I tell you something.
'Cause what's my job?
To keep your daughter safe.
Yeah. That's right.
And what's your job?
To read minds.
Can you guess what I'm thinking right now?
"I love my little girl."
That's amazing.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
How do you do that every time?
You're so good at your job.
Okay.
I'm sorry. You scared me, okay?
- You owe me a dollar. - Why?
Because you sweared.
No, I didn't. You're hearing things.
I'm not, Daddy. You sweared.
Okay, now let me put some on you.
Oh, my God. Okay, do it quickly.
- Beautiful. - Mm-hmm. Good?
- Yeah. - How's this?
You look creepy.
You mean like this?
- You mean like this, Ginger? - Dad.
No, uh, yeah. No, I get that.
Okay, go sit at the table.
No, but I-I have, I have a second source.
One minute.
Well, are you gonna ship it
or you gonna let the Times scoop us again?
-  Hi. - Hi, Mommy.
Well, so we have a deal then?
What-- This is bullshit.
You've never asked for this before.
Uh, in the time it takes to do all of this,
we could've gotten ahead of everybody.
But I just don't think we need to do it.
I promise from now on. Can you just get it online?
- Take that in the other room. - Shh.
I shouldn't be doing this.
Are you doing it or not?
Charlotte, can you take that in the other room?
Listen, I-I know what I'm doing.
You know I know because you taught me how to do it.
Goodbye, Charlotte.
Okay. Bye.
Can you, um...
Can you not do that, please?
What did I do?
I was having an important conversation with my editor.
Yeah, 'cause you're the only one
that has important stuff going on, right?
I'm not busy at all.
If I ever have kids, I'm never gonna fight in front of them.
We're not fighting, honey.
We're having a spirited exchange.
Okay.
So, um...
I just found out my dad has been finally declared deceased.
Officially, by the state of Oregon.
Um, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
How do you feel?
I mean, we knew this letter was coming one day.
But the finality of it...
Yeah, I don't know, it's still shocking.
Yeah.
Are you sad, Daddy?
I am, yeah.
I'm sad about a lot of things.
I wish I'd known him better.
But he always made me afraid of him,
so as soon as I was old enough, I left.
We hadn't spoken in a long time
because I chose not to.
Um, and now that I can't speak to him...
...I suddenly want to.
The whole day.
No way. The whole thing felt ridiculous, you know?
Oh.
I'll catch up with you guys later.
Yeah.
Hey.
This is a surprise.
I brought you some lunch.
Thank you.
We haven't done this in a while.
Yeah.
Are you happy, Charlotte?
Are-are you?
Why-why are you asking me that?
Because I don't think we're doing well right now.
I came here because
when I got that letter...
...it dawned on me
that you and Ginger are the only family that I have left.
We have such a short amount of time with people.
I just want us to enjoy each other
and try to be happy as a family while we are here.
I want to be happy, too, but...
I was thinking you should come up to Oregon with me.
I have to go up there
and pack up all my dad's stuff in a truck.
Why don't we all go together?
We'd spend the whole summer up there.
I think it'd be good for us.
It really is stunning.
There's this valley not far from the farm.
It's between these mountains.
And no matter how many times you see it,
the view makes you feel like everything's gonna be okay.
I want you and Ginger to see it.
It sounds nice, but I can't just leave work.
No, yeah, but you can work remotely.
Just take some time off.
Ginger would love that.
You could spend some time with her.
You can work on your book.
Yeah, I don't...
I don't even know if I'm good at that anymore.
You're a great writer. Come on.
I meant at spending time with my daughter.
She...
She relates to you so much more than me.
You are an incredible mother.
You are.
Come with me.
Okay, okay, I've got one.
Mm, do you live in water?
Nope.
Okay.
Do you live in the forest?
Sometimes.
Mm, can you fly?
Nope.
Do you walk on four legs?
- Yes. -Yeah?
Oh, are you a deer?
Uh... no.
Uh, are you a bear?
No.
Are you a dog?
No. I just don't know what...
Don't know the answer.
- No, I'm a fawn. - A fawn?
- Yeah. - I said deer.
- A fawn is not a deer. -It's-it's...
- It's not. - What? It's literally a baby deer.
It's not.
And fawns live in the forest. Hello.
They do sometimes, but sometimes
they're in people's backyards, so...
-Oh. Oh. -What? That's...
Oh, you are a cheater. You know what?
- That's it. You know what's coming? - Don't, Daddy. Stop.
- Daddy, stop. No, Mommy. -Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
- Tell Daddy he's being immature. - Uh-oh.
Hey, hey, I can be just as immature as he can.
Mommy, stop it. Stop, Mommy.
What makes you think I'm so mature?
- Huh? Huh? -Stop it, Mommy. Stop.
Please, Mommy, stop it.
- Mommy, stop it. -Please?
Please, Mommy, stop.
Wait, is this it? Shit.
- Dad. - Sorry, honey. Shivers.
Let me check the map here.
I have no service.
Me, either.
This does look familiar, though.
Can I see?
There's someone in that tree house.
Where?
Over there.
She's right-- there's someone inside that thing.
Oh.
Uh, let's go, Blake.
No, it's okay.
No, he has a gun.
Charlotte, everyone around here has a gun.
Blake, can-can you just please drive?
-Evening. -Hey.
Where you guys headed?
Uh, I'm looking for my dad's farm.
I just, I haven't been up here in a while. I forgot...
Who's your dad?
Uh... Grady.
Lovell.
You've been gone a long time, Blake.
Wait, do I... do I know you?
I'm Derek. I'm Dan Kiel's son.
Right.
Oh, Derek. Shit.
-Dad. - Oh, sorry.
Yeah, no, I remember you.
How are you? It's good to see you.
Not many of us left living up here anymore.
Not really a part of the world.
Yeah. I-I'd agree with that.
You might not remember this, but, uh, for the most part,
we don't like to be out after dark on the mountain.
There's no power grid, no lights.
Oh. I-I thought that was just my dad.
Uh, you know, I'm actually a little lost.
You know, I-I was sure that this was his driveway.
It's not.
Really?
It's mine.
Oh.
Yeah, okay.
Well, sorry.
The usual road to Grady's is cut off.
I'll take you there, get you settled in quicker.
Okay.
Blake, no. No, absolutely not.
- It's fine. Let him show us. - No, he...
Why can't he just tell us where it is?
- He's standing there now. - What, so...
- Just open the door, Char. - What are you talk...
- He's opening it. - Well, stop...
Hi. Hi.
Hi. Uh, no, no, no.
It's okay. I-I'll just go to the back.
Thank you, ma'am.
Watch your feet.
Just go straight on a ways.
Hey there, cutie.
Uh, Derek, that's Ginger and my wife Charlotte.
Hi.
How long you planning on staying?
-Not too long. -A little while.
It's definitely an acquired taste.
There are things you have to come to terms with up here.
Animals.
Diseases.
Well, we're, we're pretty tough people.
Is that so?
To me, you don't seem so tough.
That's a good thing.
Means you got a good life.
You're healthy, safe.
Your dad's place is just up ahead.
What do you do for a living, Blake?
I'm a writer.
I'm between jobs right now, though.
So... I'm a dad
to that monster in the back.
I'm a journalist.
I bet you look at them every day and wonder how you got so lucky
to have such a smart and beautiful family.
I do.
Shit.
Oh.
Ginger? Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Char, are you okay?
Hey, are you hurt anywhere?
Are you okay? Ginger?
Charlotte, are you hurt?
-No. -Huh?
Derek, are you okay?
Hey, hey, no, no, no, no!
Oh, shit!
Okay. We got to get out of this thing.
Ginger. Ginger.
-No, no, no. - Ginger, look at me.
No, please. Please, no.
You got to climb through the window.
Look at me, Ginger.
Climb through the window. You can do it, honey.
No, Daddy, I'm scared I'm gonna fall.
- You'll be okay. You'll be okay. - I'm gonna fall.
I'm gonna fall. I'm gonna fall.
It's okay. Just get onto the top.
Just stay right there.
Just sit right there, honey.
Just stay there, honey. Mommy's coming.
Charlotte, go.
You okay?
Stay right there. I'm coming.
I...
Okay.
We got to get down. Wait here.
Come on.
Ginger, honey, you have to go.
Come on. I'm gonna catch you.
Okay. All right, Charlotte, come on.
Are you okay?
- No, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. - Yeah?
Ginger, are you hurt at all?
-No. -Okay, come on.
We got to go. We have to find the house.
Watch your step. Come on, honey.
We got to move quick.
Where it's safer. Come on.
Careful, honey. Careful, careful, careful.
- Daddy, I'm tired. - What?
- I can't go. - Okay.
Charlotte.
Okay, honey.
Quick.
Come on, I recognize this.
We're close.
I'm gonna put you down here, honey, okay?
- Okay. - Give me your hand.
Come on.
- Come on. -Careful.
Be careful.
Come on. Come on.
This is it.
Run.
Run, honey.
Go, honey.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Daddy, hurry up.
Daddy, hurry up!
Come on. Get inside.
Wait. Wait.
- Stay right here. - Daddy, where are you going?
- I'll be right back. - Daddy. Daddy.
- Stay with Mommy. - Daddy.
Okay.
Shit.
Daddy.
Hi.
Mm. It's okay.
We're safe.
I want to go home.
I know.
We will.
We just can't go outside right now. Lay down.
We just have to wait until the morning.
Okay?
No, don't go anywhere.
Okay, okay. I'm here.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm gonna be right here. Right here.
Is that man dead?
The man who came out the tree house?
I don't know.
Most likely, he did die.
I'm so sorry that this happened to you.
It's my job to protect you.
And I didn't.
I've put you through something very scary.
And I'd never be able to forgive myself
if this stayed with you.
You know? If it scarred you.
You know, sometimes when you're a daddy,
you're so scared of your kids getting scars,
you become the thing that scars 'em.
Hey, what am I thinking right now?
"I love my little girl."
That's incredible.
You must be able to read minds,
because that's exactly what I was thinking.
Word for word.
Okay.
I love you.
I'll be right here.
Remember, that's my job.
I'm not gonna let anything happen to you.
I think we should, um...
I think we should cover the front door,
'cause if that thing... if it keeps trying to get in,
the whole door can come off the hinges.
What was it?
What?
What the fuck was that thing, Blake?
I don't know.
I know it sounded like an animal...
but I looked right at it when we almost hit it,
and I swear to God it was standing up on two feet,
like a person.
Blake.
Is that gonna hold?
Maybe.
I think we should try to call somebody for help.
How?
Hello? Test.
Hello. This is Lovell 819.
Can anyone hear me?
Hello?
Hell...
Jesus, what is that smell?
Hmm? What? What'd you say?
Hello?
Well, I found something to eat.
My dad's jerky.
My jaw. I must've hit it on the steering wheel.
Oh, fuck.
Here. Here.
Oh, my God.
Okay. Come on. Sit down.
Just sit. It's okay.
Just lift your arm.
God.
I think I cut it on the window in the truck.
I-I don't... I don't know.
This doesn't look like you got cut by glass.
Okay. Okay. Um...
Lift your arm up.
All right, j-just try a little bit. Just try.
Thank you.
Keep trying the CB radio for me.
Okay?
Jesus, Ginger.
I'm sorry I woke you, honey.
Just go back to bed, okay? You need to get your rest.
Ginger.
Will you listen to me, please?
Go back to bed. It's almost midnight.
Hey.
Did you reach anyone on the CB?
I-I don't...
I'll be done in a minute.
How odd.
Ow.
Shh.
- Charlotte. - Blake. Blake.
Blake.
Mommy.
- Get back! Get back! - Mommy. Mommy.
Get back!
Blake. Blake.
Char?
Can you read me?
Can anybody hear?
Hello?
Can anybody hear me?
This is Charlotte Lovell.
If someone can hear me, please respond.
My-my husband is, uh, sick.
Um, if-if anyone can, uh, can hear me, uh,
pl-please call someone to help.
We were attacked by some kind of animal,
and I-I think my, um, husband was infected by it.
He's...
He's not himself,
and, um, he can't, he can't talk, um...
Yeah, uh, he doesn't,
he doesn't seem to know he's sick, but, um...
i-if someone can hear what I'm saying, please help.
Uh, hello?
Hello?
Goddamn it!
I'm so worried about you.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Come on.
Let's get you upstairs.
Come on.
Here. Can you, um...
Can you write it down?
Just tell me what's wrong.
No.
You're sick-- that's all-- but we're gonna fix you.
Blake...
You're gonna get better, because Ginger needs you.
I need you.
I can't do this without you.
What I-I really want to say is...
...is that...
is that I love you, Blake.
I don't want to do anything in my life without you.
You're my best friend.
I love you so much.
Ch-Charlotte...
What is happening?
I can't understand you.
What... what are you saying?
What's wrong with him?
Hi.
It's okay.
Come here.
Daddy's not feeling well, but in the morning,
we're gonna take him to the doctor as soon as we can, okay?
Are you sick, Dada?
What is this?
Why are you bleeding?
Why is Daddy's arm like that?
- Ginger, um... - Help him, Mommy.
Baby, go to the next room, okay?
CHARLOTTE Oh, my God.
Blake.
Mommy?
Okay, come on. Come on.
Out. Just come out. It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
This way, honey.
Okay, come on. Come on.
Mommy, what if he...
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Mommy, he's coming.
Up here.
Quick. Climb up here.
Stay still.
Mommy, please.
Mommy, please, I'm gonna fall.
Come on.
- You left him. - What?
You left Daddy outside. He's gonna get hurt.
- He's gonna die! You just left him outside to die! - No. No.
No, he was trying to protect you.
Stay here.
Is it Daddy?
He's sick.
He needs us.
Open the door, Mommy.
Daddy?
Daddy...
what am I thinking right now?
What am I thinking?
I was thinking that I love you.
Daddy?
Dad? Dad, can you hear me?
Daddy? Daddy, are you okay?
I love you so much.
-Come on. Come on. Get up. Get up. Get up.
Come on. Come on.
Daddy.
Get in. Get in.
- Get in. - Mommy!
Mommy!
GINGER Mommy!
Mommy?
Why did Daddy have to get sick?
Um...
Daddy's father...
A while ago, he went out... into the forest,
and he never came back.
Everybody thought he was dead, but...
I think he just got sick.
Sick like Daddy?
Yeah.
I think he may have...
given his sickness to Daddy.
I want him back the way he was.
I know. Me, too, honey.
I-I want him back, too.
I'm always going to be here for you.
No. Mommy.
Mommy.
It's okay.
Get back! Get back! Get back!
Please, Daddy, you're scaring me.
No.
No. No.
Mommy.
In here. Come.
Come on. Come on.
Hurry, Mommy. He's coming.
Here. Just hold this.
Take it.
Come on. Come on.
All right. All right. Come on. Come on.
Mommy.
He wants this to be over.
Oh, Blake.
I'm here. I'm here.
♪ Like a shot through the dark ♪
♪ Like an arrow to my heart ♪
♪ Somewhere in your eyes ♪
♪ There's a little smoke and flame ♪
♪ I saw you change ♪
♪ And I had to rearrange it, baby ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Remember us in cars, dirty bars and dirty hearts ♪
♪ The time it takes to burn ♪
♪ I couldn't even start to think we'd be apart ♪
♪ Or a life lived in reverse ♪
♪ 'Cause somewhere back in time ♪
♪ When you and love were mine ♪
- ♪ 'Cause I saw you change ♪ - ♪ Change ♪
♪ And I had to rearrange it, baby ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I saw you change ♪
♪ You felt no pain ♪
♪ When you and love were mine ♪
- ♪ I saw you change ♪ - ♪ Change ♪
♪ Change ♪
♪ And I had to rearrange it, baby ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I saw you change ♪
- ♪ You felt no pain ♪ - ♪ Pain ♪
♪ When you and love were mine ♪
♪ And I'll see you again in red and blue ♪
♪ And I'll say it again, and I'll say it true ♪
♪ And I'll see you again ♪
♪ In red and blue. ♪